podfeed.net 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy

Podfeed.net works to protect the privacy of the individuals that visit and use. We do not target or willingly collect information on children under 13 years of age. You may visit and browse podfeed.net without providing any personal information at all. When submitting a podcast you must be a registered member. 

When becoming a registered member of podfeed.net, you will be required to provide us with a member name and email address. As a registered member we may occasionaly email you news and information from podfeed.net. You may opt-out of these notifications. We will never send you material from third parties, or sell your personal information to any third parties. 

As a member of podfeed.net, update and modify your profile at any time. Should you have any problems changing profile or unsubscribing from any mailings, please contact us at info at podfeed.net. 

**Information Automatically Logged**

At no time is your IP address used to identify you as an individual. We may use your IP address to ensure that no one from the same IP address votes for a single podcast multiple times. This is to provide accurate results to our community and prevent the skewing of results. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics using standard web analytics software 

**Cookies**

Our Site may use cookies to enhance your browsing experience by helping to remember if you are logged into the site. You may set your browser to prompt you whenever our site attempts to place a cookie on your site. You may choose whether or not to accept it at this time. 

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers, and Sponsors**

Our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

**Google Ads**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the podfeed.net privacy policy you may contact us at info at podfeed.net 

**Updates & Effective Date**

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. 

The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about October 25, 2010.
